# 你看 現在小豬跑出來啦
Look! Now the piggies are all coming out.
# 那邊鑽了一個洞
They've dug a hole there.
# 我把它搞上去 (註︰不明白甚麼叫「搞上去」，不理了)
I'll get it fixed.
# 好好吃的東西喲 快點來喲
I have something delicious! Hurry up!
# 剛好把它們騙進來啦
So I've lured them all to come back.
# 我把這關起來啦 不讓它出去啦
Let me block the way so that they can't get out anymore.
# 這一個好重啊 這個
It's really heavy, this block.
# 把這個翻起來
Turn it over.
# 這樣小豬就跑不出去啦
Then the piggies can't run away anymore.
# 這小豬會打洞的哦
The piggies can dig, you know.
# 這個洞也塞好 它會打洞
I need to fill the gap here, otherwise they'll dig.
# 好啦
Alright!
# 這樣它應該跑不出去啦
Then they shouldn't be able to run away.
# 你看 這個豬
Look! The pigs,
# 長大了不少哦
have grown up a lot.
# 你看 這個豬 長大了不少哦
Look! The pigs have grown up a lot.
# 還有這兩條小 小豬也懷孕啦
And these two, these two piggies are pregnant now.
# 小豬崽也那麼大啦
The piglets are also that big now.
# 看到我指你 它就跑 (註︰你和它是同一樣吧)
They run away once they see me pointing at you.
# 那個 吃得肚子都掉下來啦
You know, you eat so much that your belly is almost touching the ground.
# 好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
# 回家煮飯
I need to go back home and cook.